const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the ballet that takes place at Christmas?",
    answer: "nutcracker",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How many tips do traditional snowflakes have?",
    answer: "six",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "In which country is it tradition to eat KFC for Christmas dinner?",
    answer: "japan",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is traditionally hidden inside a Christmas pudding?",
    answer: "coin",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "In which country did eggnog originate?",
    answer: "britain",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What colour are mistletoe berries?",
    answer: "white",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What decoration do elves traditionally have on their shoes?",
    answer: "bells",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "What colour suit did Santa wear until Coca Cola rebranded him in red?",
    answer: "green",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What fruit is traditionally put inside a Christmas stocking?",
    answer: "orange",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the name of the snowman in Frozen?",
    answer: "olaf",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "How many Christmas trees are put in the Great Hall at Hogwarts for Christmas?",
    answer: "twelve",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Dobby made Harry a pair of socks for Christmas in year 4. What were the patterns?",
    answer: "broomsticks and snitches",
  },
];

export default questions;
